<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TWBlue</title><link>https://twblue.mcvsoftware.com/</link><description>The TWBlue official website</description><atom:link href="https://twblue.mcvsoftware.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 05:42:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>TWBlue Version 2024.5.19 has been released</title><link>https://twblue.mcvsoftware.com/posts/2024.05.19/</link><dc:creator>MCV Software</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;hello and welcome to a new TWBlue release! In this version of TWBlue, which is being released several months after the previous one, we focused on adding initial support for GoToSocial-type networks. GoToSocial is a server for creating decentralized networks similar to Mastodon. Its API is very similar but retains some differences. In this version, TWBlue can be used to log into GoToSocial accounts, although there will be some features, such as the Streaming API and Markdown support, that are not yet functional. Another significant addition is support for creating community timelines, which will allow you to load the local and public timeline of remote instances. This is useful if your instance does not federate directly with them, as it will allow you to see posts from other communities and interact directly with them. Finally, the translation module has been rewritten; it now supports using LibreTranslate by default and DeepL, for which an API key is required. Remember that if you like the project and wish to contribute to its development, you can &lt;a href="https://twblue.mcvsoftware.com/donate"&gt;make a donation.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://twblue.mcvsoftware.com/posts/2024.05.19/"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt; (2 min remaining to read)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>https://twblue.mcvsoftware.com/posts/2024.05.19/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 05:30:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TWBlue Version 2024.1.5 has been released</title><link>https://twblue.mcvsoftware.com/posts/2024.1.5/</link><dc:creator>MCV Software</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello and welcome to a new TWBlue release! This is the first version of TWBlue that we are releasing during 2024. The beginning of this year marks some important milestones, such as the project's domain change, which will transition from twblue.es to using the domain &lt;a href="https://twblue.mcvsoftware.com"&gt;twblue.mcvsoftware.com&lt;/a&gt;. This is also the initial release of TWBlue exclusively for 64-bit, as we have encountered growing issues in generating the distributable version of TWBlue on 32-bit architectures due to certain libraries used in the process no longer supporting this architecture. Finally, the generated versions of TWBlue will be published on &lt;a href="https://github.com/mcv-software/twblue/releases"&gt;GitHub Releases,&lt;/a&gt; making it easier to locate additional versions and find previous software releases. All these changes have been implemented with the aim of making the project easier to maintain, more intuitive for users, and ultimately shortening the development cycle between each release. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://twblue.mcvsoftware.com/posts/2024.1.5/"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt; (2 min remaining to read)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>https://twblue.mcvsoftware.com/posts/2024.1.5/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 14:20:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>